wakeupnow.com 2014-05-06

# PRIVACY

     PRIVACY
           And
SECURITY POLICY
  Efective March 1st, 2013

Table of Contents
Table of Contents......................................................................................................................................................................... 2
11. Your Privacy is not for sale............................................................................................................................................... 3
22. We limit the collection and use of personal information.......................................................................... 4
33. Changes to your Registration Information.......................................................................................................... 4
44. Online session information and use is only used to improve your experience ........................4
55. Third parties ofering other products or services will not be given your personal
     information without your permission.................................................................................................................... 4
66. Blogs and other Forums on WAKEUPNOW.com ........................................................................................... 4
77. Contests, Giveaways and Surveys.............................................................................................................................4
88. Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law ................................... 4
99. Your data may be transferred upon change of control but only in accordance with this
     Policy............................................................................................................................................................................................ 5
1010. You can transport or delete your data............................................................................................................... 5
1111. Email communications from us..............................................................................................................................5
1212. Your data is secure.......................................................................................................................................................... 5
1313. Our service ensures secure communications with encryption....................................................... 5
1414. You are responsible for maintaining the confdentiality of your Login ID and Password
     .......................................................................................................................................................................................................... 5
1515. We post updates on our website whenever there is a change to our Privacy and
     Security Policy........................................................................................................................................................................ 5
1616. Contact us if you have any questions or concerns.................................................................................. 5
2

At WAKEUPNOW, our most important asset is our relationship with you.
WAKEUPNOW is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of any
personal information about our users. This Privacy and Security Policy explains how we
protect personal information provided through our website www.wakeupnow.com (the
“Site”) and how we use that information in connection with our service offered through the
Site (the service). “Personal information” for purposes of this Policy mean information that
identifies you, such as your name, address, phone number, fax number or email address.
WAKEUPNOW stresses its privacy and security standards to guard against identity theft
and provide security for your personal information. We regularly re-evaluate our privacy
and security policies and adapt them as necessary to deal with new challenges.
        1.         Your Privacy is not for sale
        2.         We can limit the collection and use of personal information
        3.         Changes to your Registration Information
        4.         Online session information and use is only used to improve your
                   experience
        5.         Third parties offering you other products or services will not be given
                   your personal information without permission
        6.         Use of Blogs and other Forums on wakeupnow.com
        7.         Contests, Giveaways and Surveys
        8.         Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law
        9.         Your data may be transferred upon change of control but only in
                   accordance with this Policy
        10.        You can transport or delete your data
        11.        Email communications from us
        12.        Your data is secure and only seen by you
        13.        Our service ensure secure communications with encryption
        14.        You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Login ID
                   and Password
        15.        We post updates on our website whenever there is a change to our
                   Privacy and Security Policy
3

        16.          Contact us if you have any questions or concerns
1   1. Your Privacy is not for sale
Simply put, we do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone, for any
reason, at any time. WAKEUPNOW uses and discloses your personal information only as
follows:
    •   To analyze site usage and improve the Service;
    •   To deliver to you any administrative notices, alerts and communications relevant to
        your use of Service;
    •   To fulfill you requests for certain products and services;
    •   For market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, detecting and
        protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity;
    •   To third-party contractors that provide services to WAKEUPNOW and are bound by
        these same privacy restrictions;
    •   To enforce WAKEUPNOW’S Terms of Use; and
    •   As otherwise set forth in this Privacy and Security Policy.
In the event that you access the Service as brought to you by one of our co-brand partners,
through a co-branded URL, your email address used for registration on the Service may be
provided to that co-brand partner.
2   2. We limit the collection and use of personal information
Certain areas and features of WAKEUPNOW.com are available to you without registration or
the need to provide to us any information. However, other features of the Site or the Service
may require registration, which involves provision to WAKEUPNOW of an email address,
username, and password (collectively the “Registration Information.” In order to benefit
from the full functionality of the Service, you also must provide your third-party account
credentials (Account Credentials) to allow WAKEUPNOW to access your account data at
those other financial institutions (Account Information) for your use.
From time to time we may request other personal information to provide you with other
benefits of the Service. In all such instances, you will be given the opportunity to provide or
to decline to provide that information, and it will be used only for the stated purpose.
WAKEUPNOW may make anonymous or aggregate personal information and disclose such
data only in a non-personally identifiable manner to:
    •   Advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes,
        such as the number of users who applied for a credit card or how many users clicked
        on particular WAKEUPNOW offer;
    •   Organizations approved by WAKEUPNOW that conduct research into consumer
4

        spending; and
    •   Users of the Service for purposes of comparison of their personal financial situation
        relative to the broader community.
Such information does not identify you individually. Access to your Registration
Information, Account Credentials, Account Information and any other personal information
you provide is strictly restricted and used in accordance with specific internal procedures
and safeguard governing access, in order to operate, develop or improve the Service. These
individuals have been selected in accordance with our security policies and practices and
are bound by confidentiality obligations. They may be subject to discipline, including
termination and criminal prosecution, it they fail to meet these obligations. We may also
use third party vendors or service providers to help us provide the Service to you, such as
sending emails messages on our behalf or hosting and operating a particular feature or
functionality of the Service. Our contracts with these third parties outline the appropriate
use and handling of your information and prohibit them from using any of your personal
information for purposes unrelated to the product or service they’re providing. We require
such third parties to maintain confidentiality of the information we provide them.
3   3. Changes to your Registration Information
If your Registration Information changes while you are a customer with WAKEUPNOW, you
may update it any time via the service.
4   4. Online session information and use is only used to improve your experience
When you visit WAKEUPNOW.com, we may collect technical and navigational information,
such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time
spent on our Site. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software
compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our Web Design and functionality.
“Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored
by your Web browser on your computer’s hard drive. WAKEUPNOW may set and access
cookies on your computer to track and store preferential information about you.
WAKEUPNOW may gather information about you through cookie technology. For example,
WAKEUPNOW may assign a cookie to you, to limit the amount of times you see a particular
WAKEUPNOW Offer or to help better determine which WAKEUPNOW Offers to serve to you.
Please note that most Internet browsers will allow you to stop cookies from being stored on
your computer and to delete cookies stored on your computer. If you choose to eliminate
cookies, the full functionality of the Service may be impaired for you.
We encode our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them.
Web beacons are images embedded in a Web page or email for the purpose of measuring
and analyzing site usage and activity. WAKEUPNOW, or third party service providers acting
on our behalf, may use Web beacons to help us analyze Site usage and improve the Service.
We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For
example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online
5

campaigns or analyze visitor activity on WAKEUPNOW.com. We may permit these service
providers to use cookies and other technologies to perform these services for
WAKEUPNOW. We do not share any personal information about our customers with these
third party service providers, and these service providers do not collect such information
on our behalf. Our third party service providers are required to comply fully with this
Privacy and Security Policy.
5   5. Third parties ofering other products or services will not be given your personal
    information without your permission
There are a number of separate products and services offered by third parties advertised by
us on our Site and through the Service that may by complementary to your use of
WAKEUPNOW.com. If you choose to use these separate products or services, disclose
information to the providers, or grant them permission to collect information about you,
then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policies. You should evaluate
the practices of external service providers before deciding to use their services.
WAKEUPNOW is not responsible for their privacy practices. If you click on a link to a third
party site, WAKEUPNOW encourages you to check the privacy policy of that site.
WAKEUPNOW may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these
links have been followed and whether any action has been taken on a third party Web site.
We use this information to improve the quality of the WAKEUPNOW Offers and customized
content on the Service.
6   6. Blogs and other Forums on WAKEUPNOW.com
If you use a bulletin board, blog or chat room on our Site, you should be aware that any
information you submit there can be read, collected or used by other users and could be
used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information
you choose to submit in these forums. These forums may be hosted by WAKEUPNOW or by
one of our third party service providers on WAKEUPNOW’s behalf.
7   7. Contests, Giveaways and Surveys
From time to time, WAKUPNOW may offer you the opportunity to participate in contests,
giveaways and other promotions. Any information submitted in connection with such
activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy and Security Policy, except as
specifically set forth in the rules for those contests, giveaways or promotions. From time to
time, WAKEUPNOW may also ask you to participate in surveys designed to help
WAKEUPNOW improve the Site. Any personal information provided to WAKEUPNOW in
connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey and as elsewhere set
forth in the Policy.
8   8. Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law
Notwithstanding the foregoing, WAKEUPNOW reserves the right (and you authorize
WAKEUPNOW) to share or disclose your personal information when WAKEUPNOW
determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary or
appropriate:
6

    •  To enforce our rights against you or in connection with a breach by you of this
       Privacy and Security Policy or the WAKEUPNOW .com Terms or Use;
    •  To prevent prohibited or illegal activities; or
    •  When required by any applicable law, rule regulation, subpoena or other legal
       process.
9   9. Your data may be transferred upon change of control but only in accordance
    with this Policy
Personal information may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition,
merger, reorganization or other change of control. If we sell, merge, or transfer any part of
our business, part of the sale may include your personal information. If so, you will be
asked if you’d like to stop receiving promotional information following any change of
control.
10 10. You can transport or delete your data
Your data is yours. You can remove it anytime you want. When you request us to delete your
account for the Service, you data will be permanently expunged from our primary
production servers and further access to your account will not be possible. We will also
promptly disconnect any connection we had established to your Account Information and
delete all account credentials. However, portions of your data, consisting of aggregate data
derived from your Account Information, may remain on our production servers indefinitely.
Your data may also remain on a backup server or media. WAKEUPNOW keeps these
backups to ensure our continued ability to provide the Service to you in the event of
malfunction or damage to our primary production servers. We also reserve the right to use
any aggregated or anonymous data derived from or incorporating your personal
information.
11 11. Email communications from us
We provide our registered customers with weekly summaries of their Account Information
and email alerts. We also allow users to subscribe to email newsletters and from time to
time may transmit emails promoting WAKEUPNOW or third-party goods or services.
WAKEUPNOW.com subscribers have the ability to opt-out of receiving our promotional
emails and to terminate their newsletter subscriptions by following the instructions in the
emails. Opting out in this manner will not end transmission of service-related emails, such
as email alerts.
12 12. Your data is secure
We use a combination of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication
procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect
WAKEUPNOW.com accounts and systems from unauthorized access.
7

When your register for the Service, WAKEUPNOW requires a password from you for your
privacy and security. WAKEUPNOW transmits information such as your Registration
Information for WAKEUPNOW.com or Account Credentials securely.
Our servers are in a secure facility. Access requires multiple levels of authentication,
including biometrics recognition procedures. Security personnel monitor the system 7 days
a week, 24 hours a day.
Our databases are protected from general employee access both physically and logically. We
encrypt your Service password so that your password cannot be recovered, even by us. All
backup drives and tapes are also encrypted.
We enforce physical access controls to our buildings.
No employee may put any sensitive content on any insecure machine (i.e. nothing can be
taken from the database and put on an insecure laptop).
However, it is important to understand that these precautions apply only to our Site and
systems. We exercise no control over how your information is stored, maintained or
displayed by third parties or on third-party sites.
13 13. Our service ensures secure communications with encryption
From the time you submit your Login ID and Password, these communications between
your computer and WAKEUPNOW.com are encrypted. This enables client and server
applications to communicate in a way that is designed to prevent eavesdropping, tampering
and message forgery.
14 14. You are responsible for maintaining the confdentiality of your Login ID and
    Password
We maintain strict rules to help prevent others from guessing your password. We also
recommend that you change your password periodically. Your password must be 6-16
characters in length. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your Login ID and
Password. You may not provide these credentials to any third party. If you believe that they
have been stolen or been made known to others, you must contact us immediately at
support@wakeupnow.com, but in any even you should change your password immediately
via the Service. We are not responsible is someone else accesses your account through
Registration Information they have obtained from you or through violation by you of this
Privacy and Security Policy or the WAKEUPNOW.com Terms of Use.
If you have a security related concern, please contact us at support@wakeupnow.com. We
will work closely with you to ensure a rapid and personal response to your concerns.
15 15. We post updates on our website whenever there is a change to our Privacy and
    Security Policy
We update this Privacy and Security Policy periodically. The date last revised appears at the
top of the Policy. Changes take effect immediately upon posting.
8

16 16. Contact us if you have any questions or concerns
If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy and Security
Policy or any other privacy or security concern, send e-mail to support@wakeupnow.com.
WAKEUPNOW Inc.
504 W. 800 N.
Orem UT, 84057
801.373.2600
support@wakeupnow.com
9
